export default data = [
  {
      question: "With her teachers’ and parents’ ______, Jane regained her confidence and has made great progress.",
      options: ["construction","movement","association","encouragement"],
      correct_option: "encouragement"
  },
  {
      question: "One of Jane’s finest qualities is that she takes the ______. She always takes the necessary action and does not wait for orders.",
      options: ["initiative","charity","vision","advantage"],
      correct_option: "initiative"
  },
  {
      question: "Mr. Li is a senior ______ at a local bank. He keeps and examines financial records of people and companies.",
      options: ["volunteer","traitor","accountant","economist"],
      correct_option: "accountant"
  },
  {
      question: "Jack doesn’t look ______, but he is, in fact, excellent at sports, especially baseball.",
      options: ["athletic","graceful","enthusiastic","conscientious"],
      correct_option: "athletic"
  },
  {
      question: "The jury spent over five hours trying to decide whether the defendant is ______ or guilty.",
      options: ["evident","considerate","mature","innocent"],
      correct_option: "innocent"
  },
  {
      question: "Now that my computer is connected to the Internet, I can browse e-papers, send and receive e-mail, and ______ software.",
      options: ["upset","overcharge","undertake","download"],
      correct_option: "download"
  },
  {
      question: "The traffic on ain Street was ______ for several hours due to a car accident in which six people were injured.",
      options: ["detected","obstructed","survived","estimated"],
      correct_option: "obstructed"
  },
  {
      question: "Hundreds of people ______ in the desert storm and many more were left homeless.",
      options: ["perished","inspired","mistreated","dismissed"],
      correct_option: "perished"
  },
  {
      question: "Mike arrived at the meeting ______ at ten o’clock—as it was scheduled—not a minute early or late.",
      options: ["flexibly","punctually","numerously","approximately"],
      correct_option: "punctually"
  },
  {
      question: "A power failure ______ darkened the whole city, and it was not until two hours later that electricity was restored.",
      options: ["precisely","roughly","illogically","temporarily"],
      correct_option: "temporarily"
  },
  {
      question: "Sam couldn’t ______ how to print out the document until the teacher showed it to him.",
      options: ["go through","come up","figure out","get over"],
      correct_option: "figure out"
  },
  {
      question: "When they go for a walk, Johnny has to take long steps to ______ with his father.",
      options: ["break even","keep pace","win pride","take chance"],
      correct_option: "keep pace"
  },
  {
      question: "The man is ______ a serious nervous breakdown because he is unable to deal with pressure from daily life.",
      options: ["on behalf of","in the light of","on the verge of","in front of"],
      correct_option: "on the verge of"
  },
  {
      question: "______ treating the homeless man as a shame of the society, Mrs. Wang provided him with food and water.",
      options: ["Regardless of","As a result of","In the event of","Instead of"],
      correct_option: "Instead of"
  },
  {
      question: "Mrs. Lin ______ her husband’s complaints because, to her, facing the music is more constructive than complaining all day.",
      options: ["turned a deaf ear to","took part in","showed him the way to","took notice o"],
      correct_option: "turned a deaf ear to"
  },
]